http://www.arlingtondiocese.org/privacy-policy/

Hispanohablantes
¿Quiénes somos?
European Ministries
Native American, South American, Migrant and Hearing Impaired Ministries
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is a priority for the Catholic Diocese of Arlington (CDA). This Statement of Privacy applies to the Catholic Diocese of Arlington (CDA) and its primary website www.arlingtondiocese.org, and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Catholic Diocese of Arlington or CDA include www.arlingtondiocese.org. The CDA website is a non-profit news, information, and ecommerce site. By using the CDA website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. Collection of your Personal Information CDA will collect personally identifiable information (PII)on its site, www.arlingtondiocese.org, when you subscribe to its newsletter, register for an event, or process a donation.  To complete these transactions CDA will collect PII, such as your:   •	First and Last Name •	Mailing Address •	E-mail Address •	Phone Number   For visitors who use the site to register for a camp, such as work camp or vocations camp, CDA will also collect additional demographic and medical information, which is unique to you, such as your:   •	Age•	Gender•	Allergies•	Medical Conditions   We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for e-Newsletter account; (b) registering for an event; (c) signing up to attend or volunteer for a youth camp; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when registering or donating on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to events or donations that you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. Use of your Personal Information CDA collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.   CDA may share personally identifiable information with trusted affiliated entities (Catholic Charities of the Diocese of Arlington www.ccda.net and Arlington Catholic Herald www.catholicherald.com) also use your to inform you of other events, activities or volunteer opportunities available from CDA and its affiliates. Sharing Information with Third Parties CDA does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.   CDA may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail or provide support or assistance. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to CDA, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.   CDA may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on CDA or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of CDA; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of CDA, or the public. Tracking User Behavior CDA may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within CDA, in order to determine what CDA information or events are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content within CDA site to visitors whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. Automatically Collected Information Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by CDA. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the site, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the CDA website. Links This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. Security of your Personal Information CDA secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. CDA has a layered security infrastructure to secure your personal information both while in transit through its site and while at rest (stored) in its database.  When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocol.   We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed. Children Under Thirteen CDA does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. E-mail Communications From time to time, CDA may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication.   If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from CDA, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on the unsubscribe button. External Data Storage Sites We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted. Changes to this Statement CDA reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy. Contact Information CDA welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that CDA has not adhered to this Statement, please contact CDA at:   Information Technology OfficeCatholic Diocese of Arlington 200 N. Glebe Road Arlington, Virginia 22203   Email Address: Info.Admin@arlingtondiocese.org   Telephone number: 703-841-2500   Effective as of December 19, 2018
